[
  {
    "id": "T4A01",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is an appropriate power supply rating for a typical 50 watt output mobile FM transceiver?",
    "answers": [
      "24.0 volts at 4 amperes",
      "13.8 volts at 4 amperes",
      "24.0 volts at 12 amperes",
      "13.8 volts at 12 amperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A02",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following should be considered when selecting an accessory SWR meter?",
    "answers": [
      "The frequency and power level at which the measurements will be made",
      "The distance that the meter will be located from the antenna",
      "The types of modulation being used at the station",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A03",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Why are short, heavy-gauge wires used for a transceiver’s DC power connection?",
    "answers": [
      "To minimize voltage drop when transmitting",
      "To provide a good counterpoise for the antenna",
      "To avoid RF interference",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A04",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How are the transceiver audio input and output connected in a station configured to operate using FT8?",
    "answers": [
      "To a computer running a terminal program and connected to a terminal node controller unit",
      "To the audio input and output of a computer running WSJT-X software",
      "To an FT8 conversion unit, a keyboard, and a computer monitor",
      "To a computer connected to the FT8converter.com website"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A05",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Where should an RF power meter be installed?",
    "answers": [
      "In the feed line, between the transmitter and antenna",
      "At the power supply output",
      "In parallel with the push-to-talk line and the antenna",
      "In the power supply cable, as close as possible to the radio"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A06",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What signals are used in a computer-radio interface for digital mode operation?",
    "answers": [
      "Receive and transmit mode, status, and location",
      "Antenna and RF power",
      "Receive audio, transmit audio, and transmitter keying",
      "NMEA GPS location and DC power"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A07",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following connections is made between a computer and a transceiver to use computer software when operating digital modes?",
    "answers": [
      "Computer “line out” to transceiver push-to-talk",
      "Computer “line in” to transceiver push-to-talk",
      "Computer “line in” to transceiver speaker connector",
      "Computer “line out” to transceiver speaker connector"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A08",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following conductors is preferred for bonding at RF?",
    "answers": [
      "Copper braid removed from coaxial cable",
      "Steel wire",
      "Twisted-pair cable",
      "Flat copper strap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A09",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "How can you determine the length of time that equipment can be powered from a battery?",
    "answers": [
      "Divide the watt-hour rating of the battery by the peak power consumption of the equipment",
      "Divide the battery ampere-hour rating by the average current draw of the equipment",
      "Multiply the watts per hour consumed by the equipment by the battery power rating",
      "Multiply the square of the current rating of the battery by the input resistance of the equipment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A10",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What function is performed with a transceiver and a digital mode hot spot?",
    "answers": [
      "Communication using digital voice or data systems via the internet",
      "FT8 digital communications via AFSK",
      "RTTY encoding and decoding without a computer",
      "High-speed digital communications for meteor scatter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Where should the negative power return of a mobile transceiver be connected in a vehicle?",
    "answers": [
      "At the 12 volt battery chassis ground",
      "At the antenna mount",
      "To any metal part of the vehicle",
      "Through the transceiver’s mounting bracket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T4A12",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is an electronic keyer?",
    "answers": [
      "A device for switching antennas from transmit to receive",
      "A device for voice activated switching from receive to transmit",
      "A device that assists in manual sending of Morse code",
      "An interlock to prevent unauthorized use of a radio"
    ]
  }
]